<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fortune Teller</string>
    <string name="card_description">Card description</string>
    <string name="one_horseman">Horseman</string>
    <string name="two_clever">Clover</string>
    <string name="three_ship">Ship</string>
    <string name="four_house">House</string>
    <string name="five_tree">Tree</string>
    <string name="six_clouds">Clouds</string>
    <string name="seven_snake">Snake</string>
    <string name="eight_coffin">Coffin</string>
    <string name="nine_flowers">Bouquet</string>
    <string name="ten_sycthe">Scythe</string>
    <string name="eleven_broom">Broom</string>
    <string name="twelve_owls">Owls</string>
    <string name="threeteen_child">Child</string>
    <string name="fourteen_fox">Fox</string>
    <string name="fiveteen_bear">Bear</string>
    <string name="sixteen_stars">Stars</string>
    <string name="seventeen_stork">Stork</string>
    <string name="eighteen_dog">Dog</string>
    <string name="nineteen_tower">Tower</string>
    <string name="twenty_garden">Garden</string>
    <string name="twentyone_mountain">Mountain</string>
    <string name="twentytwo_road">Fork</string>
    <string name="twentythree_rats">Rats</string>
    <string name="twentyfour_heart">Heart</string>
    <string name="twentyfive_ring">Ring</string>
    <string name="twentysix_book">Book</string>
    <string name="twentyseven_letter">Letter</string>
    <string name="twentyeight_man">Man</string>
    <string name="twentynine_woman">Woman</string>
    <string name="thirty_lilies">Lilies</string>
    <string name="thirtyone_sun">Sun</string>
    <string name="thirtytwo_moon">Moon</string>
    <string name="thirtythree_key">Key</string>
    <string name="thirtyfour_fish">Fish</string>
    <string name="thirtyfive_anchor">Anchor</string>
    <string name="thirtysix_cross">Cross</string>


    <string name="description_one_horseman"> The card speaks of good news to come. It can also portend a message,
        which can be received in any form: e-mail, call, paper letter. The news can be both positive,
        as well as negative. This should be told by the card that lies next door.
        If the RIDER card fell out with good cards, then this always portends a good future. There will be new perspectives, everything will work out.
        The card can also portend new and imminent undertakings. You will need decisive
        actions that can lead to success, but if you do not take the initiative, then much can be lost. \n\n

        Personality. Messenger, postman, courier, witness, intermediary, promising and pleasant young man, buyer. \n\n
        Love. The organizer of wedding events, pimp, flirting, a new and interesting hobby will appear in life. \n\n
        Job. Work with the public, obtaining feedback and business documentation. \n\n
        Finance. Asset management with the help of agents, trust management of finances. \n\n
        well-being. Fitness, sports, easy and quick recovery, good health, developed thinking. \n\n
        Relationships. Depends on neighboring cards. Either the message or the events will begin to develop rapidly. \n\n
        business questions. Obtaining important information that is relevant to the business. Negotiations, business trips, contacts
        with new partners, visitor from government agencies. \n\n
        Health. Feeling satisfactory, possible respiratory and colds,
        watch your immunity. The RIDER card is responsible for the head, brain and body systems: circulatory, nervous, digestive.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_two_clever">The Lenormand CLOVER card symbolizes hope, good luck,
        short term luck. It can also portend an easy life without the hassle and worries, but she will wear a temporary
        character. It can also portend a risk, or say that it is necessary to take risks in order to achieve
        significant result.
        If the CLOVER card falls out at the very beginning of the row, then it speaks of an imminent good opportunity that you need to try
        take advantage. In general, in almost all situations, the CLOVER card indicates suddenness, surprise,
        short time of the event, so you need to be very careful and not miss the chances that will definitely appear.
        Next to unfavorable cards, it can portend losses, severe disappointments and hardships, the collapse of plans,
        which seemed to be very reliable. It may portend the beginning of a "black streak", however, usually such a bad period will not be very long.
        You will have a sense of confidence in your own
        forces, all new things will turn out well and easily. May hint at avoiding loneliness
        and connect with people as much as possible. It can be of great benefit and change your life for the better.\n\n

        Personality. Gambling, uses the slightest chance, not afraid to take risks, improviser, stuntman, swindler, has no firm convictions. \n\n
        Love. Casual kiss, multi-partner relationships, one-night stands, short-term infatuation.\n\n
        Job. Good and pleasant working conditions, holidays, the opportunity to earn extra money.\n\n
        Finance. The deal can be risky, necessary risk, attention to bookkeeping.\n\n
        well-being. Opportunity for successful conception, feeling of comfort, abundance.\n\n
        Relationships. There will be a favorable opportunity to move to the next stage of the relationship, mutual understanding and trust.\n\n
        business questions. Profit For those who are engaged in agriculture, there will be a chance to make a small profit, but some effort will be required.\n\n
        Health. You need to see a physiotherapist, the current illness will go into a milder form.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="description_three_ship">
        The Lenormand SHIP card often tells us about the appearance of good prospects, new plans. in business
        success can be expected. You can also portend a trip or a long trip that will go well.
        The SHIP also symbolizes the coming changes in life. They may be of a different nature, but they will definitely affect
        for your life. The ship can sail against the current. BUT
        it symbolizes initiative, imbalance, and generally moving against something.
        May mean hope for an improvement in the situation, in extreme cases, you will at least have the opportunity to
        change, and whether you use it or not is up to you. The SHIP card speaks properly
        about travel, trips, excursions and generally symbolize long distances that cannot be
        go on foot. In terms of psychology, the SHIP card usually indicates a desire for development, a person
        You may want to make changes in your life.
        In general, the card is favorable, however, a combination with negative cards may portend impending problems and failures.\n\n

        Personality. Merchant, Immigrant, Sailor, Sales Representative, Translator, Travel Agent, Traveler, Vacationer, Exporter.\n\n
        Love. Lover, travel romance, love can make you feel longing.\n\n
        Job. Travel related activities, foreign partners.\n\n
        Finance. Sea freight, transactions with foreign companies, export, import, financial transfers.\n\n
        well-being. The usual rhythm of life can be disturbed, traveling, life on suitcases.\n\n
        Relationships. Changes for the better. Perhaps a non-binding short but pleasant acquaintance.\n\n
        business questions. Making a profit in the field of trade, business ties will be beneficial, especially if the partners are geographically very far away. Business trips, both near and far. Negocianism.\n\n
        Health. The SHIP card means the circulatory system. Without favorable cards, it speaks of a change in the current state of health for the better. With unfavorable ones, it can even indicate death.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="description_four_house">
        The Lenormand DOM card usually symbolizes safety, security, as well as what is important for
        each person: family and close people, business, place of residence (it can even be a summer cottage).
        The HOUSE card is positive, it will soften bad cards, speak of good luck in upcoming affairs and inform
        about the successful completion of current affairs for you.
        From the point of view of psychology, the HOUSE card speaks of moral stability, courage and confidence in
        own strength. A person feels at home even in unfamiliar places and in adverse situations.
        If the card fell into the position of the past, then this indicates that your parents have a great influence on you,
        and also that the traditions that are accepted in your family are not an empty place for you.
        The HOUSE card also actually speaks of the place of residence, it can be an apartment, a cottage, a hotel,
        country house, even a tent. In addition, the card symbolizes the actual place where you live: a street, a city, or even a district.
        The cards that fall next will always be related to your home or family. By her own
        the HOUSE card is favorable, but if a combination with negative cards falls out, then this promises problems there,
        where you least want to have them: in the family or at home.\n\n

        Personality. Likes to be at home, land owner, realtor, property owner, close family, architect, interior designer.\n\n
        Love. Good neighbors, even relations in the family, everything is stable and without shocks.\n\n
        Job. Small business, artisanal production, self-employment and work from home in general.\n\n
        Finance. Family budget, home business, little money for daily expenses, mortgage lending, buying, selling or renting real estate.\n\n
        well-being. Bed rest, quarantine is possible, symbolizes hereditary and chronic diseases. On the other hand, in ones own home, the walls are treated, and there are good and favorable conditions for recovery.\n\n
        Relationships. The influence of parents on behavior in a relationship (everything is the same as that of a father or mother), the desire to create a family, traditional relationships, permanent and reliable.\n\n
        business questions. Cases related to real estate. In general, in business matters, one can hope for stability, the HOUSE card here does not portend changes in any direction.\n\n
        Health. Traditional treatments will be successful. In general, the HOUSE card symbolizes the whole body of a person as a home for his soul.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_five_tree">
        The Lenormand TREE card depicts an old tree that symbolizes wisdom, stability,
        firmness and health. A tree that has taken root deep into the earth, nothing can move it.
        The value of the WOOD card largely depends on the combination with other cards and on the position.
        If in the position of the past, then this indicates that the questioner has already realized his place in the world, he firmly
        stands on his feet and his future is very clear to him. Combined with negative cards is
        a direct order to think about the state of your health, you may need to go to the doctor and get
        unscheduled examination. Or you just need a rest, because lately you have been very
        were very tired and exhausted both physically and spiritually.
        The main meaning of the WOOD card is life. It develops steadily, albeit sometimes slowly.
        But any balance can be disturbed by external factors, a tree can be broken, it can
        demolish the hurricane, dry the drought, ignite the lightning. Such is our life. As much as we dont want to
        but not everything depends on us. For interpretation, the position of the WOOD card is of primary importance, and neighboring cards also have an influence.\n\n

        Personality. Forest or timber worker, gardener, trainer, health consultant, parents.\n\n
        Love. Pleasant relations are developing in a positive direction. A strong love that has stood the test of time.\n\n
        Job. Sick leave, joint business with family members.\n\n
        Finance. There is room for further growth, an unexpected tax, the creation of a network company, or a company with many branches.\n\n
        well-being. Natural environment, correct diet, natural products.\n\n
        Relationships. Feelings are strong and have a good basis, new relationships are promising.\n\n
        business questions. Stability and success, positions in business matters are strong and unshakable. Dont expect bad surprises.\n\n
        Health. Strong immunity, which will help to cope with almost any disease, a lot of inner strength.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_six_clouds">
       The Lenormand CLOUDS card is one of the most negative, it warns of unpleasant events that are coming
        as relentless as thunderclouds. It can be health problems, at work, in relationships and in others.
        areas of your life. But at the same time, it is worth remembering that after the rain there is always less dirt. In this sense, the CLOUDS card
        may hint that after bad events a new stage in life will begin, which can become successful. Sometimes
        people really need a reboot, albeit after sad events.
        But on the card there are both light clouds and dark ones. The cards that fall out nearby will tell you what kind of problems to expect.
        However, the influence of the CLOUDS card is usually quite short-term, because the thunderstorm not only quickly flies, but also quickly passes.
        Therefore, this card often speaks of mental instability.\n\n

        Personality. Psychologist, depressed person, pessimistic, philosopher, stepfather, meteorologist.\n\n
        Love. There are no common interests, there is understatement and misunderstanding in the relationship, one partner cannot trust the other, and keeps everything to himself.\n\n
        Job. Bad atmosphere at work, there are suspicions, envy, misunderstanding.\n\n
        Finance. Events and new information may negatively affect transactions.\n\n
        well-being. Prospects are uncertain, success will depend heavily on circumstances
        which you cannot influence. No confidence in the future.\n\n
        Relationships. Feelings will pass a very serious test of strength, all circumstances
        will be against your relationship. This does not mean that feelings have no future, it means that you need to be patient.\n\n
        business questions. The risk of large losses for reasons beyond your control (new laws,
        economic crises, political decisions). Business partners can let you down and give you problems.\n\n
        Health. The risk of a disease that will take a very long time to treat.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_seven_snake">
        The Lenormand SNAKE card has different meanings, because in different cultures to these creatures
        different attitude. She is considered a seductress, a symbol of evil, betrayal and fear.
        Sometimes they talk about it in the context of renewal, because snakes shed their skin every year. Her
        considered wise, but secretive, beautiful and possessing magical powers. Difficult to find
        another such living being, to which there would be such a different attitude.
        The appearance of the SNAKE card is usually a warning that must be heeded.
        First of all, the warning refers to your environment. There are people here who
        wish you harm and deceive you. The SNAKE card generally symbolizes lies, duplicity and betrayal. There is a threat near you.
        But to understand the meaning of this card in each scenario is not very easy. After all, the SNAKE can easily
        change their rules, break the usual order of things. Her cunning and intelligence allow her to
        make it easy and simple. The SNAKE card does not always portend serious troubles, but it
        clearly suggests that you need to be careful. Do not share your thoughts and plans,
        pay attention to what you are told.\n\n

        Personality. Lover or mistress, swindler, envious woman, femme fatale, rival, careerist, lawyer.\n\n
        Love. In love there is rivalry, there is persecution, which is more like
        courtship, but hunting. Sex is in the foreground in a relationship, and feelings are no longer so important.\n\n
        Job. Difficulties will arise at work, inventory is due.\n\n
        Finance. Fighting competitors, espionage by other companies, attempts to intercept customers.\n\n
        well-being. Fighting temptations, it is worth taking an example from someone. A person can stand up for themselves.\n\n
        Relationships. The SNAKE card symbolizes sexual energy, and in many cases this will become a strong foundation for relationships.\n\n
        business questions. Partners will violate their obligations, you may face betrayal. The shock will be strong and unexpected.\n\n
        Health. If the forecast is made for treatment, then it will be successful. Sometimes he talks about
        that drastic treatments like chemotherapy should be used.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_eight_coffin">
        The Lenormand Coffin card is one of the most unfavorable, it always promises a change
        life for the worse, portends illness, loss, protracted crises, lack of luck. With another
        On the other hand, there will always be new opportunities, because if you lose something, you can always find a new one.
        But it wont be easy either way.
        This card also speaks of the end of a certain period, the current stage of your life is coming to an end.
        and the next one will start soon. But there is a risk of reaching a dead end, the way out of which will require a lot of strength and energy.\n\n

        Personality. A person is stuck in his past, work is related to the past (for example, an archaeologist), a person from the past.\n\n
        Love. The romance will end, the lover will leave.\n\n
        Job. Reductions at the enterprise, deadlines are running out.\n\n
        Finance. Financial losses, problems in business up to bankruptcy. Inheritance is possible.\n\n
        well-being. Long rest required, lack of energy, lethargy.\n\n
        Relationships. The final break in relations, or they continue, but by inertia, as feelings will die.\n\n
        business questions. Lack of prospects, losing contracts, loss of money, failed partnerships.\n\n
        Health. In terms of health, the GROB card is one of the most unfavorable. It may portend a serious illness up to death.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_nine_flowers">
        The Lenormand BOUQUET card depicts flowers, which are a symbol of happiness. You will
        smile good luck in everyday affairs, especially this card is favorable for women. Can
        expect special attention from a partner, unexpected and very pleasant gifts. Generally
        the BOUQUET card portends excellent health, excellent mood and an optimistic attitude.
        In matters of the heart, the BOUQUET card portends good news: a new relationship will begin, current
        will move to a new stage of development, new impulses will appear. But dont forget that
        that flowers in bouquets are short-lived, they wither pretty quickly, which makes this card a symbol
        impermanence. Everything is temporary and nothing lasts forever. BOUQUET greatly affects neighboring cards,
        radiates kindness and positive energy to them. The influence of negative cards softens, even
        when it comes to the worst combinations.
        Often speaks of actually receiving a gift, which does not have to be material.
        Recognition of merit is also a good gift. The BOUQUET card symbolizes beauty,
        harmony, naturalness. Talks about original ideas, attractive appearance
        form. Sometimes promises wealth and a merry life.\n\n

        Personality. Bride, work related to beauty or flowers, artist, cheerful woman stepmother.\n\n
        Love. Good couple, harmonious relationship.\n\n
        Job. A lot of work, nice interior in the office.\n\n
        Finance. Good attitude, which can sometimes turn into flattery, commercial bribery, gifts that can be bribes.\n\n
        well-being. Grooming, cosmetic surgery, beauty requires sacrifice.\n\n
        Relationships. New relationships will begin, or old ones will receive an additional impetus for development.\n\n
        business questions. Income will increase, circumstances are favorable for business development.\n\n
        Health. If there is a disease, then it will soon be cured without consequences, in general, the state of health is good, good health.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_ten_sycthe">
        The Lenormand Spit card is a serious warning that you need to pay attention to.
        attention is a must. She warns of what will be required of you
        prudence and a wise look at surrounding things. Only this will help, if not avoided,
        then seriously mitigate future troubles.
        The KOSA card very often warns of injuries, accidents and accidents. Danger will come
        unexpectedly, from where you did not expect it at all. Neighboring good cards can soften
        consequences, and in some cases even prevent the occurrence of a bad situation,
        but in any case, in the near future it is worth being as careful as possible. Forewarned is forearmed.
        KOSA also says that any dangerous situation must be responded to very quickly,
        but thoughtfully. The cards that fell on the right can give you a hint about what you can do.
        help. Also, nearby cards can tell you where to expect danger from.\n\n

        Personality. Surgeon, insurance agent, professional who handles sharp instruments (e.g. hairdresser), warehouse worker, executioner, radicalized person, war veteran.\n\n
        Love. Portends a breakup, the partner will leave you. Nothing good can be expected from a lover.\n\n
        Job. Wage cuts, chances of working overtime without adequate pay, reduced work hours.\n\n
        Finance. Termination of the contract after difficult negotiations, decrease in the number of transactions and sales.\n\n
        well-being. Costs will decrease, see a surgeon, need a break.\n\n
        Relationships. Relations are bad, there is a misunderstanding, a serious conflict is looming that could lead to a break in relations.\n\n
        business questions. The occurrence of dangerous situations, there will be chances of losing everything. Avoid the slightest risk, work only with trusted partners. Bad time to develop.\n\n
        Health. There is a high chance of injury, the need to urgently seek medical attention, treatment can no longer be postponed.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_eleven_broom">
The Lenormand Broom card usually speaks of a quarrel. The main reason is the lack of harmony
        in the family, misunderstanding and numerous conflicts. In some cases, the card promises punishment
        for perfect deeds, sometimes says that the people around you cannot understand you, you
        no reliable friends.
        On the other hand, the BROOM is a symbol of cleansing, it sweeps away everything superfluous, it just does it
        too rough. She not only sweeps out all the garbage, but also reveals the secret.
        Its neutral value indicates a reboot, that the current situation will become clearer.
        But in combination with other cards, most often it portends conflicts at work, in the family, quarrels with friends.\n\n

        Personality. Judge, official, janitor, janitor, civil servant, likes to provoke, agitates.\n\n
        Love. Relationships will end, homosexuality, perverted tastes in sex.\n\n
        Job. Trouble awaits at work. Long discussions and even disputes over work matters.\n\n
        Finance. Negotiations with partners, review of deals.\n\n
        well-being. Purification, irritability, training.\n\n
        Relationships. Serious quarrel, unsuccessful marriage, lack of understanding, conflicts both in the family and with friends.\n\n
        business questions. Quarrel between business partners, layoffs, trouble with management.\n\n
        Health. The Broom card is responsible for diseases of the nervous system, but in general, it is very unfavorable in matters of health, as it promises a severe course of the disease and a difficult cure.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twelve_owls">
The Lenormand OWL card symbolizes minor troubles and difficulties that may arise.
        daily. You just need to keep doing what you are doing and this period will pass. Not worth it
        let trifling problems affect your life.
        The OWL card just says that small troubles easily deprive you of your soul.
        balance, you start to fuss too much, in stressful situations you lose
        the ability to make sound and thoughtful decisions.
        OWLS also directly indicate oral speech, which can be both a live conversation and
        telephone communication. The card also symbolizes rumors, empty talk, gossip,
        people who like to "wash the bones".\n\n

        Personality. Small trader, barker, stage performer, dentist, story teller, informer, salesman, bore.\n\n
        Love. Private dates, good and tender relationship.\n\n
        Job. Endless chatter in the office, worries in the workplace, online shopping.\n\n
        Finance. Promotion of goods on the market, an interview with a business publication.\n\n
        well-being. A visit to a speech therapist, sore throat, throat problems, treatments may not be available to you.\n\n
        Relationships. Doubts, lack of confidence in yourself or in a partner, quick reassessment of the situation, the likelihood of disappointment.\n\n
        business questions. You need to check everything again, you are very close to making the wrong decision. Its best to refrain from important activities altogether.\n\n
        Health. Even if nothing hurts and your health does not bother you, it is better to consult a doctor and undergo an examination. Perhaps there is a hidden disease that needs to be treated before its too late.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_threeteen_child">
      The Lenormand CHILD card is favorable. First of all, she talks about
        that you are at the beginning of the journey, and there are a lot of opportunities ahead. The most important
        use them, things wont do themselves. If you willingly and easily perceive
        new ideas, then you have very good prospects. It also symbolizes trust
        but if there are bad cards nearby, then in this case we are talking about naivety, which often harms
        the questioner. You shouldnt trust everyone. Often talks about the birth of a child.
        The CHILD card indicates a person who does not yet have experience, makes mistakes and
        he needs control. He has not yet matured emotionally, which is very often
        leads to problems. The CHILD card also says that events will happen
        in the very near future.

        Personality. Child, teenager, mentally handicapped person, caregiver, student.\n\n
        Love. Age difference between partners, sincere and pure feelings.\n\n
        Job. A new colleague will show up, minor assignments from management, a job that doesnt require much skill.\n\n
        Finance. Research project, search for benefits. Savings that have been accumulated since childhood or youth.\n\n
        well-being. Easy attitude to life, a person knows how to enjoy the simplest things. Something will have to be started from the very beginning, it may also indicate the appearance of the disease in the initial stage.\n\n
        Relationships. Romance, the beginning of serious and strong feelings, true love. With bad cards, it speaks of infantility and lack of maturity, which can interfere with relationships. It also directly indicates the imminent birth of a child.\n\n
        business questions. For a new business, you do not have enough knowledge, you need to think about additional education or enlist the support of experienced people. The ability to start all over again.\n\n
        Health. Underdevelopment, internal organs have not formed properly, which may indicate chronic diseases.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_fourteen_fox">
        The Lenormand FOX card symbolizes cunning, cunning, numerous temptations, deceit,
        intrigue, the desire to achieve goals through deception. You are near a trap and she is very cunning, you need to
        be very careful not to fall into it. Evil is near you, some peoples intentions
        deceitful, they want to use you. The problem is that it can be very difficult to recognize all this.
        The FOX card warns that you need to be careful in communication, do not talk too much,
        any information can be used against you. If the fox is smart and experienced, then she will survive
        in any situation, her resourcefulness and ability to manipulate will not allow her to be caught.
        Also, the FOX card indicates the ethical side of business relationships, where possible different
        options, such as team rivalry or a normal business environment. Also
        symbolizes cunning and determination, and these instincts can be useful. If a
        use them at the right time and to achieve specific goals.
        But in general, the FOX card warns you to be careful and that your plans and thoughts
        must be kept to yourself. Even if someone initially does not have evil intentions,
        they may appear when he gets the right opportunity.\n\n

        Personality. Rogue, criminal, liar, swindler, consumer, child, investigator, spy, cunning person.\n\n
        Love. There is deceit in the relationship, treason is possible. There are various minor problems in the family, most often they are caused by distrust or closeness.\n\n
        Job. The work is not very interesting, there is no desire to build a career, a bad leader who does not have the necessary qualifications.\n\n
        Finance. Espionage by competitors. There are scammers nearby, there is a catch in transactions or contracts. Things are not going well in general.\n\n
        well-being. Idleness or taking care of yourself and your life, satisfaction of basic needs.\n\n
        Relationships. Deception, betrayal, intrigue, someone is trying to win your favor and insidiously take advantage of this.\n\n
        business questions. The ability to look for various loopholes and cunning will help you in trading. Opportunities to take advantage of.\n\n
        Health. Medical errors, the disease is difficult to determine. Mild cold, fever.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_fiveteen_bear">
        The Lenormand BEAR card indicates the strength, nobility and courage that are needed
        to achieve lofty goals. If it falls out with bad cards, then this indicates that you
        want to do harm, and the main motives are envy and jealousy, or simply
        deep dislike. At the same time, the enemy is not so easy to recognize, often you think
        that he is a friend, but in reality this is not at all the case.
        Also, the BEAR card can indicate something very big, something that can even scare.
        It can be daily duties that begin to weigh down and fall on you.
        a heavy load, which is becoming more and more difficult to carry. But in general the BEAR is
        a symbol of strength that will come to the rescue and protect. But in some cases it may
        suppress you, you will feel dependent on the patron and lose faith
        in the fact that you yourself are the ways to cope with your troubles.
        The BEAR card can mean material well-being, which also depends on someone.
        If there are deadlines in fortune-telling, then the BEAR speaks of a long period of stability.
        In general, if the alignment is not the most pleasant, then you can count on the presence of a patron,
        which, if not solve all your problems, then at least help mitigate their consequences.
        But at the same time, you should not share your plans even with close people.\n\n

        Personality. Guardian, parents, boss, lawyer, strong athlete, grandmother, owner, influential friend, mother, petty criminal.\n\n
        Love. Long-term relationship, your partner is generous, strong love.\n\n
        Job. The position is associated with great responsibility, the boss likes to grumble.\n\n
        Finance. Time for promising projects and big ambitions. Negotiations from a position of strength.\n\n
        well-being. Physical exercise, playing sports in general, self-confidence, endurance.\n\n
        Relationships. Either you take care of your partner and are a good and reliable patron for him, or vice versa. BEAR speaks of care, concern and empathy.\n\n
        business questions. A stable position, there are strong partners who have influence and they are able to help your business.\n\n
        Health. Strong immunity, the body has enough of its own strength to cope with almost any disease.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_sixteen_stars">
        The Lenormand STARS card is happy, it speaks of hope, future success.
        You will experience elation, inspiration will come, but she also often warns
        that unexpected successes can turn anyones head. Sometimes its worth it
        stay who you are and miss the stars from the sky. Your goals must be clear
        correspond to your capabilities, do not indulge in pipe dreams or wish
        what you dont really need.
        With unfavorable cards, STARS promise failure, there is a risk of making a mistake. With good
        with cards, you should count on luck in any business.\n\n

        Personality. Astrologer, creative person, inspirer, engaged in science, likes to dream, is in search, famous person, artist.\n\n
        Love. Mutual love based on trust. Inspirational feelings.\n\n
        Job. The set goals will be achieved, success awaits in work, everything will be given very easily.\n\n
        Finance. Charity, effort rewards, grants.\n\n
        well-being. Keeping the promises you made to yourself, there is complete self-confidence that guarantees success.\n\n
        Relationships. Sublime feelings, romance.\n\n
        business questions. The STAR card is weakly connected with the material, it can talk about scientific developments or important discoveries. She does not actually predict income, except that she promises good long-term prospects.\n\n
        Health. Satisfactory state of health, if there is a disease, it will soon go away. Physiotherapy.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_seventeen_stork">
        The Lenormand STORK card is a symbol of recurring changes, happiness and native places. Often she
        means following traditions, observing principles. Can talk about the birth of a child, or about future changes
        in life, which will lead to important consequences. If the deal with bad cards, then this is already
        indicates a change for the worse.
        Where or where to expect changes will be prompted by the card that fell in front of the stork. The card that fell after
        describe the nature of these changes. If we are talking about timing, then STORK talks about cyclicality and
        equal periods. That is, something can be repeated at the same intervals.
        But in general, the STORK card portends that the current situation will move forward. Not necessarily in
        for the better, but change will come anyway. It can also refer to a person
        whose main task is to take care of other people.\n\n

        Personality. Doctor, teacher, family man, guard or overseer, baby, lawyer, carrier, close relatives.\n\n
        love. Meeting and getting to know a new partner, relationships will develop, a high probability of getting an offer, an early wedding.\n\n
        job. The company will get an impetus for development, working conditions will improve, you need to focus on training new colleagues.\n\n
        finance. Active search for investments, price fluctuations.\n\n
        well-being. Changes for the better, infertility treatment will be successful.\n\n
        Relationships. The birth or conception of a child, the relationship will reach a new level. Meet your love.\n\n
        business questions. Trade will bring profit, a long business trip that will be successful. Profitable connections with foreign partners.\n\n
        health. Feeling better, get well soon. Sometimes the STORK card says that you need to go to a sanatorium or a medical resort. Or just a change of scenery for a while, it will be very useful.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_eighteen_dog">
        The Lenormand DOG card is a symbol of friendship, as well as help, mutual assistance and protection.
        She points to a reliable friend, a person who is trustworthy, he will not leave
        you at a difficult time. Next to good cards, a DOG promises good luck, and next to bad cards
        warns that your environment is not as good as you used to think.
        The DOG card also often advises you to follow your instincts, the very first impulse will be the surest.
        This will help to avoid problems or solve them with minimal losses. In this arrangement, she
        warns of the upcoming difficult period in life, but the situation will still remain with you
        under control, you just need to make an effort and solve it in your favor.
        In some layouts, the DOG card hints at a friend who really needs your help.
        Often friends are in a very unpleasant situation, but at the same time they are embarrassed to ask for help.
        Be careful, your help is needed.\n\n

        Personality. Best friend, good acquaintance, brother, neighbor, consultant, fellow traveler, companionship, willing to help, business partner, animal trainer or animal handler.\n\n
        Love. Very close relationship, maybe platonic. Very rarely indicates incest.\n\n
        Job. Partner at work, teamwork.\n\n
        Finance. Transactions will be reliable, partnership is beneficial for both parties. It is worth following the companys predetermined course of development.\n\n
        well-being. Training, everyday small things, outside help.\n\n
        Relationships. True friendship, feelings can develop into strong love. The partner is faithful to you and ready for self-sacrifice, your happiness comes first for him.\n\n
        business questions. In business, expect success, third-party circumstances will not be able to interfere. Good work by subordinates, loyal companions.\n\n
        Health. Rehabilitation, wounds heal very quickly. A hint of the use of folk remedies, herbal tinctures and other drugs without chemicals in the treatment.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_nineteen_tower">
        The Lenormand TOWER card symbolizes the end of the matter, the achievement of the long-awaited result.
        Often we can talk about the business of a lifetime, on which a lot of time has been spent and
        labor. Also, the TOWER is a symbol of resistance to external factors, a state of stability.
        Often it portends longevity and happy years of life.
        If the TOWER card falls next to bad cards, then its value becomes negative.
        We should expect problems with money, illness, a series of failures. Achieving goals can
        require a lot of strength from you, like climbing the highest tower.
        Sometimes the TOWER card can be understood as a symbol of isolation and solitude, which may be the result of a breakup.
        Also indicates official institutions, government buildings, or the city.\n\n

        Personality. An aged person, an official, an official, a government official, a philosopher, a leader, a law enforcement officer, a patriarch, an architect, a father or grandfather.\n\n
        Love. Relationships have notes of patronage, love between people of different social status, which in some cases can interfere.\n\n
        Job. Bureaucracy, enforcement of rules.\n\n
        Finance. Taxes, budget money.\n\n
        well-being. Indicates possible isolation, medical facility. Has organizer abilities.\n\n
        Relationships. Strong and strong feelings that can last until the end of days, but without much emotion and romance. Just a good and practical relationship, it could all point to a marriage of convenience.\n\n
        business questions. Stability in everything. A solid place in the market, competitors will not be able to harm you.\n\n
        Health. Long years of life, a stable condition, if there is a disease, it will go away or go into a chronic stage, but it will not cause much inconvenience.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twenty_garden">
        The Lenorman GARDEN card, also sometimes referred to as the PARK, is a symbol of pleasant
        pastime, rest in good company, festive event. She often
        promises to receive an invitation or go to an event where you will be easy and fun.
        Also, the SAD card can talk about illusions, excessive self-confidence and even complacency.
        In a word, she warns of too high self-esteem, and this is always fraught with
        bad consequences. Do not think too much of yourself and too well, perhaps
        it is not so and the fall will be very unpleasant.
        The GARDEN card means everything related to relaxation, from a walk along the promenade to a hike in the night
        club or football match. Often it symbolizes large gatherings of people in different
        reasons, these may not necessarily be festive events, such may be a parade, a rally, etc.
        This card usually softens the effect of bad cards. But its effect is not too strong, so
        if the alignment as a whole promises trouble, then the SAD card will only slightly alleviate them.\n\n

        Personality. Socialite, artist, fashionista, party-goer, gardener, works with paintings, prefers to work in a team.\n\n
        Love. New spontaneous acquaintances, events with a favorable atmosphere for dating.\n\n
        Job. Corporate, vacation, trip with colleagues to nature.\n\n
        Finance. Public relations, the economic situation is generally favorable, sometimes you can expect an improvement in the financial situation.\n\n
        well-being. A trip to nature or to a country house, a period of recuperation, long-term communication.\n\n
        Relationships. An equal union, even and quite reliable. Sometimes a SAD card can indicate that a couple thinks too much about the opinions of others and tries to conform to generally accepted norms.\n\n
        business questions. Useful acquaintances at official events, good partnerships. Mutual benefit. It is worth following fashion, following everything new.\n\n
        Health. Favorable card in matters of health. With bad cards, it indicates that psychology is the cause of diseases, you need to be less nervous and take care of your nerves.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentyone_mountain">
        The Lenormand MOUNTAINS card portends obstacles in your path. It can be as nasty
        circumstances, as well as people who put spokes in your wheels. Most often the mountain will
        impregnable, so you need to either wait or look for a workaround. The smart one will not go uphill, the smart one will bypass the mountain.
        The MOUNTAIN card is also a symbol of immobility, but the desire to climb the mountain indicates that
        that you are ready to solve your problems. Fate has challenged you, but its too early to give up.
        The path will be difficult, but it must be passed. Or take a detour. In addition, fast
        climbing a mountain is fraught with loss of strength and falling from a great height, and this hints at the fact that
        that overconfidence is harmful.
        In some cases, the MOUNTAIN card symbolizes reliable and unshakable protection, shelter from bad
        situations. In the layout, the cards that fell on the left will indicate a dead end, these paths need
        avoid. The cards that fell on the right indicate that the indicated difficulties are left behind.\n\n

        Personality. Athlete, geologist, miner, precious metal worker, stonemason, builder, superintendent, industrial climber, powerful person, rival to be feared.\n\n
        Love. A temporary break in relations, celibacy is possible. Attempts to save the relationship may fail.\n\n
        Job. A very serious project, the work is very tiring, complex tasks, hard and hard work.\n\n
        Finance. Large companies or monopolies dictate their terms to you, you have to work in a disadvantageous situation. Loss of money.\n\n
        well-being. Difficult period, patience is needed.\n\n
        Relationships. There is a wall of misunderstanding between you, it will be difficult to overcome it. Relationships have no prospects.\n\n
        business questions. Double meaning. In combination with good cards, it promises success in business that will go uphill. With bad cards, it portends a sharp descent, problems, obstacles.\n\n
        Health. In matters of health, the MOUNTAIN card has only a negative meaning and indicates diseases. Most often, these are diseases that prevent the body from functioning normally. May indicate blood clots, etc. You may have trouble conceiving or giving birth.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentytwo_road">
        The Lenormand FORKING card indicates that a decision will soon need to be made.
        Neighboring cards may suggest in which area it will have to be received. But in any
        In this case, you will have several options to choose from and it will be difficult to choose the right solution.
        The FORKING card also speaks of the end of a stage in life, a new, but unknown, awaits ahead,
        which can scare and cause sadness. Doubts can get in your way, but you need to remember that
        choice will have to be made anyway. If there are bad cards nearby, then this is an obvious
        hint: you are going to choose a bad option. If there are good cards nearby, then
        you just need to think a little and the choice will be right.
        The choice can wait for you anywhere, also the FORKING card often hints not at the actual choice,
        but a large number of options. For example, different sources of income, easy relationships
        with two people at once and doubts about who is better to choose. surrounds you
        ambiguity and this must be reconciled. Its just a stage in your life that
        happens to every person.\n\n


        Personality. A tourist, a person with two jobs, an amateur, a vagabond or a beggar, a hunter, loves
        travel, stranger.\n\n
        Love. You are loved, but you do not know this person. Relationships dont develop. You will meet a traveling companion.\n\n
        Job. Opportunity to earn extra money at another job, a large number of different tasks, you will have to work for yourself and for that guy.\n\n
        Finance. There are several possibilities, its time to evaluate the methods of work. Partners or clients hesitate.\n\n
        well-being. A midlife crisis is coming. Hobbies will not be superfluous. A choice that will affect the rest of your life.\n\n
        Relationships. The situation cannot be decided in any way, it is necessary to understand the feelings and make a choice, it cannot continue like this. Sometimes the FORK indicates a love triangle.\n\n
        business questions. Promising ways for further development. Looking for compromise options when you need to please several at once.\n\n
        Health. Treatment directly depends on the qualifications of the doctor and the correct diagnosis. But the diagnosis can be ambiguous and imply different options.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentythree_rats">
        The Lenorman RAT card portends problems with property. It could be damage
        or missing. You can become a victim of thieves. It is worth checking all household appliances,
        water pipes and wiring. Do not carry a wallet with a large amount of money,
        and keep it in the inside pocket.
        With bad RAT cards, it means that it will not be possible to make up for the loss. Rare layouts with
        good cards portend the return of the lost. Everyone knows that RATS not only know how to
        survive in any conditions, but also differ in greed and gluttony. That is why this
        the card is a sign of serious losses and losses.
        Losses can be in any area of your life, usually this is indicated by combinations with other cards,
        the decoding of which you will find below. The nature of the loss is directly indicated by the card that fell after the RAT.\n\n

        Personality. Criminal, thief, marauder, beggar, buys stolen goods, pessimistic, energy vampire, money launderer.\n\n
        Love. The risk of colliding with the gigolo. Relationships in general only bring disappointment.\n\n
        Job. Lack of free money, all salary goes to current expenses.\n\n
        Finance. Loss of money, risk of becoming a victim of fraud, problems with accounting.\n\n
        well-being. Decrease in the level and quality of life due to stressful situations, weight loss, physical and spiritual exhaustion.\n\n
        Relationships. Not the best relationship, partners neglect each others interests.\n\n
        business questions. Big trouble, financial loss, partners want to deceive you. Theft risk.\n\n
        Health. In terms of health, a bad card that promises serious illnesses and difficult treatment. It also often indicates problems with digestion and the fact that the disease will become chronic.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentyfour_heart">
        The Lenormand HEART card is very good. It symbolizes love, true friendship,
        excellent mood. If the relationship already exists, then they will receive a new impetus for development,
        if they are not there, then a pleasant meeting should be expected soon. The appearance of this card
        promises favorable opportunities in other areas of your life.
        But with bad cards, the HEART can warn of anger, hatred, endings.
        relationship or a serious crisis between partners. As they say "Out of love"
        hatred is only one step away and it all comes from the heart. Bad cards around
        are often a hint that you need to pay more attention to your partner,
        All is not lost, and if the relationship is truly dear to you, then you can keep it.\n\n

        Personality. Lover, psychologist, hopeless romantic, suitor, cardiologist, fun person.\n\n
        Love. Light flirting, date invitation, very auspicious time for love.\n\n
        Job. You get satisfaction from work, the manager supports you in everything and even turns a blind eye to your jambs. Promotion.\n\n
        Finance. Philanthropy, spending money on good causes.\n\n
        well-being. Doing what you love gives you good emotions.\n\n
        Relationships. New relationships, increased feelings. A novel that you will remember for the rest of your life, regardless of its outcome.\n\n
        business questions. There is little logic in relations with partners, much more personal feelings. Decisions are often made spontaneously. In some cases, this can be harmful, business requires a cool head, not a warm heart.\n\n
        Health. With bad cards, he speaks of heart disease.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentyfive_ring">
        The Lenormand RING card directly indicates marriage. If she fell in the position of the past,
        then the marriage has already taken place, if she is in the position of the future, then the marriage is yet to come.
        She often talks about the obligations that each partner in a relationship has to make.
        take yourself. They will require a responsible and serious approach.
        If fortune-telling is for daily affairs, then the RING portends the conclusion of an agreement, the basis
        which will be trust, predisposition to each other. partnerships will
        successful, except when bad adjacent cards directly portend the opposite.
        Most often this portends a new love, but in general, this is a good omen,
        you can expect success in many things.
        As a symbol of unions, the RING card often indicates contracts or agreements.
        But never forget the responsibilities you have taken on. Not worth it
        let down a partner who really trusts you. With some cards
        to say that the union will not be very reliable.
        The RING card often combines adjacent cards, in this sense its interpretation can
        sometimes be quite complicated. But if positive cards fell out, then this is one of the best
        options for you. Regardless of what you are planning.\n

        Personality. Lawyer, witness, securities holder, mediator, minister.\n\n
        Love. Romance in relationships, mutual understanding. All problems are solved together.\n\n
        Job. Indicates teamwork.\n\n
        Finance. Starting joint ventures, signing contracts, agreements and obligations that will be fulfilled more often.\n\n
        well-being. Your biorhythms match. You need to take care of your health.\n\n
        Relationships. Wedding or engagement. The beginning of a very strong relationship can also indicate true friendship, which is important for both parties.\n\n
        business questions. The conclusion of an agreement, a profitable partnership.\n\n
        Health. Listen to the doctors recommendations, now is the time to think about your health.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentysix_book">
        The Lenormand BOOK card has many meanings.
        Fundamental - teaching, discoveries, solving riddles, discovering secrets. It could be
        information that is intentionally withheld from you. Very often she advises getting new ones.
        knowledge that can bring you great benefits and change your life in the future.
        A hint at the importance of education, which can be obtained throughout life. After all, even in retirement
        you can learn something new.
        Also, the BOOK card symbolizes secrets, mysteries. For people who cant read
        books are a real mystery. But this should not be taken literally, here it is possible
        figurative meaning, for example, "to read the book of life." And this requires special literacy.\n\n

        Personality. An educated person, a teacher, an employee of a bookmakers office.\n\n
        Love. Relationships in which there is no love, or hidden love. Sometimes love is according to all the canons, that is, the right one.\n\n
        Job. Indicates office space, paperwork, preparation of reports and reports.\n\n
        Finance. Accounting, work with numbers in documents.\n\n
        well-being. It is recommended to follow the regimen, read a lot, train your memory.\n\n
        Relationships. Relationship with a difficult person who has closed in on himself. Secret romance. But such a relationship can have a very promising future, you just need to help your partner open up and you will not regret the patience and efforts expended.\n\n
        business questions. A hint that before solving a problem, it needs to be studied from all sides, to delve into all the details. Only this will allow the situation to be resolved in your favor. Also in this case, the BOOK can act as an indication of further education.\n\n
        Health. In matters of health, the card is bad, it says that diseases are difficult to diagnose, and sometimes they occur in such a form that a person cannot understand that he is sick for a long time. Difficulties in making a correct diagnosis.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentyseven_letter">
        The Lenormand LETTER card symbolizes the receipt of documents, in this sense, its interpretation
        simple enough. It can also be a message in a different form: email, oral communication.
        Neighboring cards can tell you what kind of news to expect, it can be very
        positive news, and extremely bad, or neutral.
        The message may be formal or informal. Also, the LETTER card may portend the receipt
        parcels, important information will come. Or it may be a very insignificant piece of news that
        will have no effect on your life. Much depends on the combination with other cards.\n\n

        Personality. Courier, messenger, postman, works in the information field, journalist or blogger, friends in social networks, secretary, office worker.\n\n
        Love. Love messages, there is a lot of romance in the lyrics.\n\n
        Job. Unemployment benefit. It may also indicate job duties, an interview, or professional suitability.\n\n
        Finance. Youll have to deal with bureaucracy.\n\n
        well-being. Follow the regime, go through a medical examination.\n\n
        Relationships. The letter contains a message that only applies to two people, the others do not need to know. May indicate pen pal.\n\n
        business questions. Papers that are directly related to current affairs.\n\n
        Health. The card is neutral.\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentyeight_man">
        Card Lenormand MAN means son, father. If a woman is guessing, then this indicates
        to a lover, husband or close friend. Can represent a man who
        the woman is interested.
        In some layouts, the MAN card shows that in the life of the asker there is an active
        a man takes part.
        But in general, the MAN card is neutral and simply indicates a person.\n\n

        Personality. Dad, husband, son, friend, fiance partner, boss, family supporter, lover.\n\n
        Love. Good sex, your lover is just a sample of a real man. Also just points to a real man.\n\n
        Job. Mens work, solidarity among men, mens team.\n\n
        Finance. Client signing agreement.\n\n
        well-being. Masculinity, but sometimes vice versa, complaints from a man. Purposefulness and energy.\n\n
        Relationships. Relationships continue thanks to the man. Can talk about the appearance of an opponent, especially if a man is guessing.\n\n
        business questions. You understand the fullness of your responsibility and are ready to make any decisions.\n\n
        Health. For women, it speaks of hormonal surges. For a man - problems with potency.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_twentynine_woman">
        The Lenormand WOMAN card symbolizes the female gender. If the object of divination is a man,
        then she points to an important woman in his life. It can be a sister, daughter, mother, wife.
        In general, the card is neutral and simply indicates a woman.
        The cards that are nearby will help you understand exactly who the WOMAN points to, and
        also determine character and other qualities.\n\n

        Personality. Girlfriend, wife, teacher, daughter, female boss, fiancee.\n\n
        Love. A woman who is loved. Life companion.\n\n
        Job. Business lady, self-realization, efficient work.\n\n
        Finance. Manages the family budget, purchases necessary goods. Career focused.\n\n
        well-being. Conditions generally favorable, may indicate gynecology.\n\n
        Relationships. Self-affirmation through guardianship, a woman plays the role of a mother. Also, the WOMAN card can warn that there is a rival, or that a mother or other female relative interferes in the relationship.\n\n
        business questions. It is recommended to rely on your intuition and trust your instincts. Non-standard solutions that do not always follow from logic can bring success. Good time to compromise. Powerful woman.\n\n
        Health. For a man, it promises hormonal problems. For a woman, gynecological problems.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirty_lilies">
        The Lenormand LILY card is usually lucky. She shows what is good around you.
        environment, a favorable period in your life, there will be a lot of joy. Symbolizes
        the road to your dream and your ideals, portends a long and happy life.
        Surrounded by negative cards, it portends conflicts, an unsuccessful period in life, internal disharmony.
        You can fall into disgrace from which it will be very difficult to get out, you will experience
        self-doubt.
        Also, the LILY card symbolizes harmony, wisdom and experience that has been accumulated over the years. It may
        point to a person who will give valuable advice, or someone needs your participation.
        Sometimes the card speaks of passion, and sometimes vice versa, of rigid self-control. Relatively
        time indicates a leisurely development, the time frame is usually 3-4 months. But the result
        that was achieved gradually will last for a long time.\n\n

        Personality. Sponsor, experienced and mature person, head of the family, passionate, patron and protector, judge, exemplary family man.\n\n
        Love. A lover who is much older, there is a lot of passion in the relationship. May indicate a divorced man or a widower.\n\n
        Job. Retired, experienced and distinguished colleagues.\n\n
        Finance. Improved well-being in general.\n\n
        well-being. Retirement is coming, the reasoning is slow and mature.\n\n
        Relationships. Beautiful, chic relationship. A lot of romance, a real bouquet of feelings. Love blooms with all colors. Spiritual closeness.\n\n
        business questions. Absolute honesty, a real chivalrous spirit, you can not expect a dirty trick. Also, LILIES often indicate that you are minding your own business and you need to continue moving in the chosen direction.\n\n
        Health. predicts successful treatment. Sometimes it is a harbinger of food poisoning.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtyone_sun">
        The Lenormand SUN card symbolizes light and heat, energy that will be enough to
        perform any actions and complete cases. We should expect a very favorable period, good luck,
        fame, new acquisitions and achievements. Wishes will come true, there will be good health
        and always in a great mood. Neighboring cards will tell you exactly where to expect good things.
        Also, the SUN card symbolizes stability, because our luminary has been appearing in the sky for billions
        years, and the night is always followed by dawn. He says that they will help you even in a difficult
        situations. Promises inspiration, an excellent period for self-realization and the beginning of new plans.
        The SUN softens bad cards, if the alignment turned out to be too negative, then this can be understood,
        as a need to endure. Then the SUN will rise and it will be much easier. Not worth it
        indulge in despondency, troubles are temporary, and if you make an effort, then
        they run out much faster.
        Often indicates warmth, it can be summer, good weather, a resort. Or too much energy
        to be applied as intended. The SUN has a good effect on the card that fell
        in front of it, practically neutralizes the negative, makes the neutral positive,
        and the good action will become even brighter. But this is not always true for the card,
        which fell after the SUN. In individual combinations, problems cannot be avoided, but the consequences
        will still be much softer.
        If you get the SUN card, then you can safely start new business, success will accompany you.\n\n


        Personality. An optimistic person, the soul of the company, has a great influence, initiator, pioneer (in every sense).\n\n
        Love. Relationships without worries and hassles, strong love that will overcome any adversity.\n\n
        Job. Light work, workplace near the window.\n\n
        Finance. Good interest, positive times, no money problems.\n\n
        well-being. Tanning, solarium, quick healing, relaxation.\n\n
        Relationships. A very warm relationship in which love and respect for each other comes first. These are very mature and measured feelings, your partner has the most serious intentions. It is also possible that it will help you fulfill yourself (or vice versa).\n\n
        business questions. Success, career will go uphill, patronage.\n\n
        Health. If the main issue in divination is treatment, then the SUN is one of the most favorable cards. He speaks either of good health, or of a quick cure without consequences. Good immunity, no predisposition to disease.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtytwo_moon">
        The Lenormand MOON card often speaks of variability, because the Earths satellite every month
        changes its shape. Often in the layout, this card has a double meaning. On the one hand, this
        thirst for adventure, the desire to have fun, but on the other hand it can be interpreted,
        as the need to set aside time to rest and reflect on life.
        The LUNA card applies to work as well as to the decisions we make in the workplace or
        choosing your career. If you want promotion, recognition and success, then you need to apply
        maximum effort, you have no other options. The moon itself is not a source of light, it
        reflects the light of the Sun, so this card can be taken as a symbol of the reflection of everything
        what are we doing.
        Do not forget that the MOON can be growing, which hints at growth, and maybe
        decreasing, which indicates losses. But its all the same, its always been and always will be.\n

        Personality. Caretaker, career-focused, passer-by, daydreaming.\n\n
        Love. Romantic, imaginative partner, very sensitive.\n\n
        Job. The work is related to creativity, perhaps work at night.\n\n
        Finance. Fluctuations in the market, period of instability.\n\n
        well-being. Food for thought, shifting emotional state.\n\n
        Relationships. Depends on surrounding cards. If they are good, then the MOON promises peace and warmth. If negative, then we should expect an unstable period, a disregard for people.\n\n
        business questions. Habitual activities, following traditions. During this period, it is better not to change anything, otherwise you risk incurring losses.\n\n
        Health. Disease of the kidneys or genitourinary system. Gynecology.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtythree_key">
        The Lenormand KEY card most often means a way out of the situation, in which direction is another question,
        but the main thing is that you solve the current problems and the next stage of your life will begin. Yes sometimes
        a person does not know what is behind the door, but this is not always a good reason to leave it closed.
        Often indicates a key issue, the solution of which can change the whole life as a whole. it
        there may be a problem that has prevented you from living a normal life for a very long time.
        The KEY card advises telling the truth. Sometimes a third party will be needed to solve an unpleasant situation.
        help, but if people dont know you have a problem, how can they help you? worth being
        decisive, otherwise you will never achieve your goals.
        Next to the bad cards, the KEY says that the exit has not yet been discovered or that you have chosen
        wrong option. Perhaps this is a reason to replay everything back. Usually the appearance of this
        cards can clarify the situation and give an answer to the question that was asked.\n\n

        Personality. Reliable person, working in the field of security, strategic thinking, prison guard.\n\n
        Love. Unusual love, extraordinary relationship.\n\n
        Job. Brainstorming will be required to resolve the issue, you need to work according to the strategy.\n\n
        Finance. Realization of potential, successful decisions in the field of finance.\n\n
        well-being. Realization of potential.\n\n
        Relationships. Solving pressing problems, moving to the next level. There are no stereotypes in the relationship, there is emancipation. Fall of inner barriers.\n\n
        business questions. An alternative approach, non-standard actions will lead to success. The start of a new project destined to be successful.\n\n
        Health. The method of treatment chosen is correct, recovery can be expected. Rarely indicates dentures.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtyfour_fish">
The Lenormand FISH card is good in terms of plans and hopes for the future.
        Nothing will just happen, but all your efforts will not be wasted and the result will be achieved.
        The card can be a symbol of the end of the path, success achieved. You have caught your fish.
        Combined with bad cards, it means that your plans are too ambitious and do not match.
        opportunities. You are probably in a bad environment that prevents you from realizing yourself.
        All new beginnings will not end very well, very often you will be let down by people who
        you trusted completely in vain.
        But most often, the FISH card promises money, lucrative contracts and an improvement in financial standing.
        It is associated with trade, purchase and sale of property, various transactions. Sometimes it can only mean water.\n\n

        Personality. Fisherman, businessman, merchant, financier, pawnbroker.\n\n
        Love. Sharing finances, expect matchmakers to visit, you are a good match.\n\n
        Job. Respectable work, provides the necessary means of subsistence. Work experience, work book.\n\n
        Finance. Trading deals, cashing out money, selling liquid assets.\n\n
        well-being. Rest by the sea, sports.\n\n
        Relationships. Feelings are strong, however, calculation also takes place. But it often makes the relationship even stronger.\n\n
        business questions. Profits, investments will be profitable, things will go uphill.\n\n
        Health. With bad cards, it indicates colds, problems with blood vessels, as well as hidden diseases that quietly eat up health, but it is very difficult to identify them.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtyfive_anchor">
        The Lenormand ANCHOR card symbolizes the stability and immutability of the situation, which in some
        It can be a big plus in some cases and a minus in others. Of course, stability is only bad
        when the situation as a whole is unpleasant, when there is a black streak in life. But more often the ANCHOR is
        a symbol of constancy in a positive way.
        Much depends on combinations with other cards, they will tell you which situation will be unchanged.
        Also, the ANCHOR card often indicates a balanced person who tends to think about his decisions.\n\n

        Personality. Nurse, heir, workaholic, self-employed, mediator, insurance agent.\n\n
        Love. Relations are equal, or they have already exhausted themselves. We need to stop them or look for ways to develop them. May indicate true love and loyalty to the grave.\n\n
        Job. Routine, a large number of small things that do not allow you to relax. Tedious work.\n\n
        Finance. Stability.\n
        well-being. Relationships are convenient for everyone, routine, there are useful connections.\n\n
        Relationships. Trust and devotion. stable relationship. With bad cards, it speaks of boredom, that someons relationship is burdensome or tired.\n\n
        business questions. The material base is strong, the business is reliable. You can count on partners.\n\n
        Health. Regarding health issues, the ANCHOR card is neutral. Rarely indicates that diseases will become chronic.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description_thirtysix_cross">
The Lenormand CROSS card is very strong, it affects the entire alignment. It often portends
        torment, suffering and hard times. Symbolizes the end of one period and the beginning
        next. Change will not be easy, but not always for the worse, you need to look here
        to other cards. The CROSS very often tests us for strength, for how we endure
        tests that fate itself sent.
        The CROSS card portends a change in worldview, a rejection of plans, a revision of views on many things.
        Reassessment of values, understanding of reality - all this awaits us in the near future. Herself
        in itself, the card is negative, but with bad ones it acquires a terrible meaning. With many combinations
        changes for the worse are inevitable. But do not despair, the black stripe is always replaced by a white one.\n\n

        Personality. Rescuer, chronic loser, committed to his ideals, boss, often the scapegoat.\n\n
        Love. Difficult relationship, there is a misunderstanding.\n\n
        Job. Remote work, freelance, self-employment. Any work outside the team.\n\n
        Finance. Short-term loans, loan repayment.\n\n
        well-being. Difficult period, however, there are new opportunities. Unstable emotional state.\n\n
        Relationships. A very serious test of love lies ahead.\n\n
        business questions. For business, the card is sharply negative. Sometimes its better to quit a lost cause and start over than trying to revive a corpse.\n\n
        Health. Severe disease, possible complications up to disability. The CREST card often indicates that the disease did not come just like that. This is punishment for the mistakes of the past.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="shuffle">Shuffle</string>
    <string name="lenorman">Lenormand</string>
    <string name="ask_question">Ask a question</string>
    <string name="get_answer">Get an answer</string>
    <string name="how_read_cards">How to guess on the cards?</string>
    <string name="instruction">
        Instruction: \n
        Think of a question, if the question contains the name of a person, then pronounce his full name,
        Shuffle the cards as many times as you see fit
        either click on the "Shuffle" button, or just shake the phone).
        When you finish shuffling the cards, scroll through the deck and click on the ones you see fit.
        In total, you need to choose 3 cards.
        After you select all the cards, click on the picture of the card and read the values. Try to link all three cards in one answer to your question.
        It may not work at first, but then you will learn.\n\n
        Do not take this application seriously, predictions may or may not come true. Think of it as just entertainment.

    </string>
</resources>